[{"answer": " Oh... Hi, honey... my friend, uh, uh, my friend", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend, right.  My wife, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Rent.  You're late", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Kit give me nothin'", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Fine", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend.  My name is my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You may feel more comfortable. This is not the kind of place that rents rooms by the hour", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Every place has hookers, but if this hotel has hookers, they don't look like they're..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Well, now that you have me for the night, what are you going to do with me", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Do you plan everything", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm not just talking about sex", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Three thousand for five days. And my friend, I will let you go", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " 'Lo", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I was asleep.  You woke me.  You okay", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm just going to my room", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I think you'll find it normal enough", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You'll like it fine", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Actually, some of the richest people I know have the worst manners.  Of course, Mr. my friend, being of old money, knows his way around a table.  All right now, pay attention please.  Salad fork", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They will serve salad", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What if they serve soup", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "But what if they serve soup", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't think so.  You should know we're going to fight you with every resource we have", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I do.  I take it all very personally.  Very nice meeting you, my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Television", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I have work to do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's this box, it has pictures, sound.  You don't have to use your brain at all", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "U", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Offer nine and a half.  Bring them back down to earth", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Someone's loaning it to him. Get on it right away", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No, I'm sorry, I don't", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " I'm sorry, am I being too forward", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'd like to find out.  You don't know anything about me either. That's why people have lunch", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Business", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I got tired of hating my father", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It felt good", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Look I just wanted to say goodbye", "docId": "Pretty-Woman.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yeah, well, I check out today", "qsentId": 40}]